

Contact



099-113-6768



rnutthawut1919@gmail.com



Nonthaburi

Languange

- Thai (Native)
- English (Intermediate)

Skills

- Mysql
- Python
- Microsoft Excel
- Power Bi
- HTML&CSS
- Tableau
- Nodejs (Learning)

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Adaptability
- Curiosity
- Social Quotient

Certificate

Fundamental of Computer Programming with Python Language (2022)

Thai MOOC:LMS

MOS: MS Excel 2013 (2022)

Thai MOOC:LMS

Microsoft Power BI (2022)

Thai MOOC:LMS

NUTTHAWUT RUENGSRI

About Me

My name is Nutthawut Ruengsri, also known as "Unun". I have experience in Python and Excel. I am dedicated to self-improvement, highly motivated, and have a strong interest in web development. I work well with others and adapt quickly. I am currently practising algorithms using Python and plan to learn more programming languages to enhance my skills in the future.

Education

High School, Sciences and Mathematics Program

May 2016 – March 2020 - Watrajabopit school

Bachelor's Degree in Science and Technology, Major Data Science.

June 2020 – February 2024 - Rajamangala University Phra Nakhon.

Second Honor Degree (GPA 3.64)

EXPERIENCES

Cloud Computing (2022)

- Create a Compute Engine.
- Manage Virtualization Network.
- Install Jupyter Notebook on Compute Engine.
- Customize Jupyter Notebook to work with SSL.

Digital image data analysis (2022)

- Experience in Digital Image Data Analysis using Keras, TensorFlow, Imutils, MTCNN, OpenCV, NumPy, and OS
- Developed Deep Learning models for Mask Detection and Facial Expression Analysis
- Utilized Imutils, MTCNN, OpenCV, and NumPy for image processing tasks

Intern at Information Technology Center Department of Disaster Prevention and Mitigation Ministry of Interior.

June 2023 - October 2023

- Make a Dashboard about Drought in the Tableau program.
- Make a Dashboard about Flood in the Tableau program.
- Help organize a meeting the project to develop the potential of information and communication technology personnel.
- Help organize a meeting the project using radio frequency synthesis equipment.

Excel Data Analysis (2023)

- Using Excel functions such as SUM, AVERAGE, MIN, MAX, COUNT, IF, SUMIF, COUNTIF, and VLOOKUP for data manipulation and analysis.
- Skilled in creating Pivot Tables and Pivot Charts to summarize and visualize complex data sets, enabling insightful decision-making.

Final Project with Python January 2024 - February 2024

- Use a Python model (RandomForestClassifier) to predict flooding.
- Utilize Streamlit to deploy it on the web.